{
    "subject": "resource/Caract\u00e8res",
    "predicate": "property/style",
    "object": "resource/Sans-serif",
    "human_readable": "The style of Caract\u00e8res is Sans-serif.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8531438708305359,
            "question": "Are there any other design elements that complement the sans-serif style in Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8354684710502625,
            "question": "Is Caract\u00e8res written in a serif or sans-serif font?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8197147250175476,
            "question": "What visual impact does the sans-serif style have on the reading experience of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8103861808776855,
            "question": "What is the style of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6009503602981567,
            "question": "Why do you think the author chose a sans-serif font for Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5365645885467529,
            "question": "Can you describe the font style used for Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4268249571323395,
            "question": "What kind of typography is associated with Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4043845534324646,
            "question": "How would you characterize the appearance of the text in Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3751780092716217,
            "question": "How does the font style of Caract\u00e8res contribute to its overall aesthetic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3552158772945404,
            "question": "Give an example of a font that shares similarities with the style of Caract\u00e8res."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The style of Caract\u00e8res is Sans-serif.",
            "html": "dbpedia_108_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does the font style of Caract\u00e8res contribute to its overall aesthetic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_108_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you characterize the appearance of the text in Caract\u00e8res?",
            "html": "dbpedia_108_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of typography is associated with Caract\u00e8res?",
            "html": "dbpedia_108_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_108_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nWhile the documents discuss serif and sans-serif typefaces extensively, they do not mention \"Caract\u00e8res\" or its style.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe text mentions \"caract\u00e8res sans serif\" and provides examples like Helvetica, Arial, and Futura which are sans-serif fonts. This supports the statement that the style of Caract\u00e8res is Sans-serif."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text discusses the use of serif and sans-serif typefaces in various contexts, including design recommendations and historical trends. It highlights the popularity of sans-serif fonts in digital media and branding for their modern and clean aesthetic. Conversely, there's a growing trend towards using serif fonts to add charm and character to brands. This suggests that the distinction between serif and sans-serif is important and actively considered in design choices.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}